<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?><Questions>	<Question Num="1">		<![CDATA[What speed do you drive?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[first gear]]><Cars><Car id="5" /><Car id="9" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[second gear]]><Cars><Car id="6" /><Car id="7" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[third gear]]><Cars><Car id="2" /><Car id="4" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[fourth gear]]><Cars><Car id="10" /><Car id="3" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[fifth gear]]><Cars><Car id="1" /><Car id="8" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="2">		<![CDATA[What color car do you like?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[red]]><Cars><Car id="1" /><Car id="8" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[blue]]><Cars><Car id="6" /><Car id="3" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[green]]><Cars><Car id="9" /><Car id="2" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[yellow]]><Cars><Car id="7" /><Car id="8" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[torquoise]]><Cars><Car id="10" /><Car id="4" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="3">		<![CDATA[What kind of cars do you like?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[classic]]><Cars><Car id="4" /><Car id="6" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[fast]]><Cars><Car id="1" /><Car id="10" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[foreign]]><Cars><Car id="9" /><Car id="3" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[domestic]]><Cars><Car id="2" /><Car id="5" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[flashy]]><Cars><Car id="7" /><Car id="8" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="4">		<![CDATA[Where would you get your next car?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[next door neighbors]]><Cars><Car id="9" /><Car id="5" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[used car lot]]><Cars><Car id="2" /><Car id="6" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[private dealer]]><Cars><Car id="10" /><Car id="7" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[high-end dealership]]><Cars><Car id="1" /><Car id="8" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[eBay.com]]><Cars><Car id="4" /><Car id="6" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="5">		<![CDATA[Where would you take a date in your car?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[drive-in]]><Cars><Car id="10" /><Car id="9" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[moonlight ride]]><Cars><Car id="6" /><Car id="3" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[lover's lane]]><Cars><Car id="7" /><Car id="4" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[vegas]]><Cars><Car id="1" /><Car id="8" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[car rally]]><Cars><Car id="2" /><Car id="5" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="6">		<![CDATA[Beside owning a great car, the most important thing in life is...]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[good looks]]><Cars><Car id="3" /><Car id="7" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[personality]]><Cars><Car id="6" /><Car id="5" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[money]]><Cars><Car id="8" /><Car id="1" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[love]]><Cars><Car id="4" /><Car id="7" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[friendship]]><Cars><Car id="2" /><Car id="9" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="7">		<![CDATA[If your best friend crashed your car, what would you do?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[forgive and forget]]><Cars><Car id="4" /><Car id="9" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[sue your friend]]><Cars><Car id="8" /><Car id="3" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[stay mad for a day]]><Cars><Car id="6" /><Car id="5" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[get mad and get even]]><Cars><Car id="1" /><Car id="2" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[make your friend buy you a new car]]><Cars><Car id="7" /><Car id="10" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="8">		<![CDATA[If you bought a new car, who would you take riding in it first?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[your mother]]><Cars><Car id="4" /><Car id="6" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[your girlfriend]]><Cars><Car id="3" /><Car id="7" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[your boss]]><Cars><Car id="1" /><Car id="8" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[your dog]]><Cars><Car id="5" /><Car id="2" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[your friend]]><Cars><Car id="9" /><Car id="10" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="9">		<![CDATA[What kind of seat covers would you buy?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[leopard print]]><Cars><Car id="3" /><Car id="4" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[leather]]><Cars><Car id="1" /><Car id="6" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[sheep fur]]><Cars><Car id="9" /><Car id="2" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[pleather]]><Cars><Car id="8" /><Car id="5" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[pin stripes print]]><Cars><Car id="7" /><Car id="10" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question>	<Question Num="10">		<![CDATA[What's your favorite car accessory?]]>		<Answers>			<Answer Num="1"><![CDATA[speakers]]><Cars><Car id="10" /><Car id="9" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="2"><![CDATA[rims]]><Cars><Car id="8" /><Car id="7" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="3"><![CDATA[air conditioning]]><Cars><Car id="6" /><Car id="5" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="4"><![CDATA[tv screens]]><Cars><Car id="4" /><Car id="3" /></Cars></Answer>			<Answer Num="5"><![CDATA[GPS system]]><Cars><Car id="2" /><Car id="1" /></Cars></Answer>		</Answers>	</Question></Questions><Cars>	<Car id="1" src="im_1.jpg">		<![CDATA[McQueen]]>		<![CDATA[Lightning McQueen is a hotshot rookie racecar, poised to become the youngest car ever to win the Piston Cup Championship. He has just two things on his mind: winning and the perks that come with it. Fame, money, groupies, helicopters... it's everything he's dreamed of, but that's about to change. When McQueen gets lost in the forgotten town of Radiator Springs, he's introduced to a group of new friends that challenge him to reconsider the car he wants to be.]]>	</Car>	<Car id="2" src="im_2.jpg">		<![CDATA[Sarge]]>		<![CDATA[Sarge is a 1942 WW2 Willy's Army Jeep, a patriotic veteran to the core. He proudly flies the Stars and Stripes and begins each day with a rousing rendition of Reveille. If he's not busy running the local army surplus store, Sarge's Surplus Hut, he can often be found precisely manicuring the lawn in front of his Quonset hut. When he's not working, Sarge spends his time arguing with his next door neighbor, Fillmore. Truth be told, Sarge knows that his life is more interesting with Fillmore in it to "question authority."]]>	</Car>	<Car id="3" src="im_3.jpg">		<![CDATA[Sally]]>		<![CDATA[Sally is a beautiful 2002 Porsche 911 from California who grew tired of life in the fast lane and made a new start in the small town of Radiator Springs. Charming, intelligent, and witty, she is the town attorney and the car most dedicated to preserving and reviving the town with the hopes that one day it will get "back on the map."]]>	</Car>	<Car id="4" src="im_4.jpg">		<![CDATA[Flo]]>		<![CDATA[Flo is a 1950's show car - a sassy, no-nonsense lady, with the biggest heart in town.  She runs the local diner, Flo's V-8 Cafe, the only gas station for miles around, where she still serves the "finest fuel in fifty states."  While traveling across country as a glamorous Motorama girl, Flo passed through Radiator Springs and met Ramone. It was love at first sight and the two have been married ever since.]]>	</Car>	<Car id="5" src="im_5.jpg">		<![CDATA[Mater]]>		<![CDATA[Mater is a good ol' boy with a big heart and the only tow truck in Radiator Springs. Mater runs Tow-Mater Towing and Salvage and manages the local impound lot. Though a little rusty, he has the quickest towrope in Carburetor County and is always the first to lend a helping hand. Mater sees the bright side of any situation and is the first to befriend McQueen.]]>	</Car>	<Car id="6" src="im_6.jpg">		<![CDATA[Doc]]>		<![CDATA[Doc Hudson is a 1951 Hudson Hornet, a seemingly quiet country doctor who runs the local "medical clinic" (mechanic shop) in Radiator Springs. Though he's a car of few words, Doc is respected and admired by the townsfolk for the way he looks out for their health and tends to their aches and pains. Doc ends up teaching McQueen lessons he can apply both on and off the track.]]>	</Car>	<Car id="7" src="im_7.jpg">		<![CDATA[Ramone]]>		<![CDATA[Ramone is a 1959 Impala low-rider who owns and operates Ramone's House of Body Art, the local custom body and paint shop.  Ramone is an artist - a true magician with paint and metal, but he hasn't had anyone to paint in years.  So for now, his only canvas is himself; he repaints himself daily.]]>	</Car>	<Car id="8" src="im_8.jpg">		<![CDATA[Chick]]>		<![CDATA[Chick Hicks is a racing veteran with a chip on his shoulder, a ruthless competitor who has cheated his way into more second-place finishes than any other car. He's the consummate runner-up, always finishing just behind the world's greatest racing champion, The King. Chick's been living in The King's shadow for years, but he's ready to make his move. He's convinced that this will be "the beginning of the Chick era." The only thing standing in his way now is Lightning McQueen, the hotshot rookie.]]>	</Car>	<Car id="9" src="im_9.jpg">		<![CDATA[Fillmore]]>		<![CDATA[Fillmore is a 1960 VW Bus and Radiator Springs' resident hippie.  A believer in individuality and all things natural, he brews his own organic fuel and preaches its many benefits.  Visitors can try Fillmore's special flavors in the tasting room behind his love-bead and tie-dye-covered geodesic dome. His many conspiracy theories and "naturally" unkempt yard drive his neighbor Sarge, a veteran army jeep, absolutely nuts.]]>	</Car>	<Car id="10" src="im_10.jpg">		<![CDATA[King]]>		<![CDATA[The King, Strip Weathers, is a 1970 Plymouth Superbird and a racing legend. He has won more Piston Cup races than any other car in history, but has managed to keep his priorities straight. He's a down-home guy who knows that it takes more than trophies to make a true champion. Above all else, The King values hard work and sticking together as a team. He is planning on retiring at the end of the season and Lightning McQueen would give up just about anything to fill his treads.]]>	</Car></Cars><End>	<![CDATA[<a href="asfunction:clickHere">CLICK HERE</a> to add your personality match image to your MySpace page.]]></End>